CONTACT

ADAM T'KOY

a.p.tkoy@gmail.com 630-363-0924

DATA ANALYST AND SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

With a strong foundation in computer science, I quickly adjust to new programming languages and problem solving challenges. I will push myself to achieve worthy goals. Most of all, I love to collaborate because working with amazing people has been the highlight of all my prior career experiences.

SKILLS

- Programming in C, C++, Java, OCaml, Python, and R with IDEs like Visual Studio and Xcode
- Analyzing data to produce summary findings and visualizations
- Took lead as front-end developer for semester-long project creating web app with React, Node.js and Javascript
- · Completed additional coursework outside degree in SQL and Swift programming
- Version control with GitHub

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF ILLINOIS URBANA-CHAMPAIGN. AUGUST 2024

Bachelor of Science, Statistics and Computer Science, 3.91 GPA

EXPERIENCE

GENIUS ADMIN. MAR 2022 - AUG 2023

Apple Store, Naperville, IL

- Resolved issues for in-store repairs
- Managed information and progress of repairs sent to offsite facility
- Collaborated across store teams to ensure excellent customer experiences
- Maintained organization and inventory of repair room

APPLE CAREER EXPERIENCE, JAN 2023 - JUN 2023

Apple, Inc., Cupertino, CA

Supported the Manufacturing Quality Engineering, Color team for 5 months, full-time:

- Operated special equipment to measure samples for color and texture
- Cleaned and manipulated data in Tableau to generate summary reports and visualizations
- Assisted in sample reviews with Industrial Design team
- Sorted, labeled and stored part samples for archive

PRODUCT SPECIALIST, NOV 2019 - MAR 2022

Apple Store, Naperville, IL

Efficiently created solutions for customers, including scheduling repair/support appointments, recommending and transacting purchases, and facilitating initial device set up

PROGRAM SUPPORT SPECIALIST, DEC 2017 - NOV 2019

College of DuPage, Glen Ellyn, IL

- Analyzed student data to create and update statistical reports each semester
- Updated 3 internal data resource websites using HTML